<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Realty One Triad]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Realty One Triad]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/realty-one-triad/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 17:31:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/realty-one-triad/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Testimonials]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Testimonials</h1><p>Realty One was extremely helpful and responsive. They provided us with many recommendations, from recommended repairs/upgrades to staging to listing. By following their recommendations, we were able to get a great offer within 1 week of listing! Great experience all around.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5239779db3a8060dab50467ff0b0c2caebad6e85.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.realtyonetriad.com/testimonials.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d2ffd012-8f4d-4ac6-aac5-1029a855a1c9</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 17:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Realty One was extremely helpful and responsive. They provided us with many recommendations, from recommended repairs/upgrades to staging to listing.  By following their recommendations, we were able to get a great offer within 1 week of listing! Great experience all around.  Josh A  My wife and I were very pleased with how you worked to make the transition as pleasant as possible. You were very helpful in answering our questions.  We would recommend you to anyone looking for a pleasant experience and helpful agent. Thanks again for your hard work . . . we are enjoying our new home. Michael & Tanya T  They did an outstanding job in a tough market. They are very professional and have a good eye for what could be impeding your sale. We highly recommend them!  Robert & Joanne P  Realty One was able to help me sell my home in a difficult market and with a house that was located on a busy road.  Their communication was excellent, we were traveling for business at the time, and they kept us up to date on everything that was happening.  After selling my house, Realty One was then able to help negotiate a great deal on a townhouse for us. Which we are delighted with.  Joy P  Realty One has done an excellent job helping us sell and buy our new home.  From the beginning, they were very direct in letting us know what we needed to do to give us the best opportunity to sell our house.  Removing over sized furniture, painting neutral colors and having a competitive/realistic Listing Price all made a huge difference.  Within three weeks of listing, we were under contract. During the new home search, they were very flexible and accommodating to our schedule.  We were already very familiar with the city and neighborhoods, so they did not have to make too many recommendations - however - they did a  very good job helping us compare/contrast several very different houses we were comfortable with. Matt & Danielle W  We chose to list with Realty One after failing to sell our house while listed with two of the areas top producing agents in terms of sales. We couldn't have been happier with them. We were under contract within a couple of months. We were living out of state at the time and simply could not have  accomplished everything that needed to be done without their help. They were in constant communication with us. We always felt informed.  I firmly believe that if we had listed with another we would still be saddled with our house. We would recommend them without hesitation.  Kevin & Andrea H  Realty One did a great job in selling my property.  They were very persistent even when we had a first contract fall through because the buyer couldn't get financing.  As an out of town seller they even coordinated repairs and upgrades that needed to be performed.  I would recommend them to anyone looking to buy or sell a house in the Piedmont Triad area.  Nathan  They were great to work with in selling our home.  Within 30 days of having it on the market we were under contract.  They do a wonderful job in helping you understand the process of selling and what options are out there for you.  I would highly recommend them to any of my friends, family and co-workers. Wendy M  Realty One was very straight forward about what needed to be done in order for the property to sell.  Very respectful of any personal attachments toward what was a home but also practical about the reality of the market. Incredibly diligent and committed.  If I was still in the area I would not think twice before recruiting their expertise again.  Anthony T  Realty One was a huge help to us in buying our first home.  Being first time home buyers we were not sure of the process, they walked us through the process explaining everything!  They were flexible to meet with us. We flew in from out of state over a long weekend and they showed us several houses.  By the time we left that weekend we had purchased a house! Being from out of state this was very helpful!  We have already recommended Realty One to several people and will continue to in the future! Carolyn and Kyle J  After having my house on the market for 6 months with another agent/company, I felt it was time for a change.  Realty One was recommended by a friend at work. They explained the different ways they marketed the property and how the photos of the house  can make a difference - the quality, the order presented on websites, etc. We were fortunate to sell our home very close to our asking price.  Realty One was always prompt in responding to our calls and emails. They were helpful in suggesting simple, inexpensive improvements to make to our home.  They were also great in the negotiation process and the whole closing process.  Sam & Susan K  Realty One was great, very attentive to my needs and wants as a home buyer/seller.  They were very patient and genuinely cared about making sure I found the right house which I did. Would highly recommend.  Nick A  We have bought and sold several homes in the past ten years and Realty One was, by far, the easiest company to work with.  They made us comfortable with the entire process, shared their opinion as needed and respected ours.  The pictures they took of our home were outstanding and definitely made the house stand out online.  I would highly recommend them to anyone looking for a dedicated and realistic real estate company to sell their home. Thanks for everything Realty One!  Andy & Tonya P  Realty One sold our home within a few weeks.  They offered suggestions along the way to help us sell the house faster and it definitely worked.  They were very easy going and great to work with and listened to everything I had or wanted to say. Would definitely recommend them.  Christine L  We have bought and sold many homes over the years.  Realty One is one of the absolute best real estate companies one could ask for.  They were very responsive to our needs and helped us find the perfect home.  I could not have asked for better representation and would not hesitate to refer anyone looking to buy or sell a home to them!  David B  I was very impressed with Realty One. I have had other real estate agents who just made the listing and then never called and communicated.  They called at least once a month to let me know how everything was going.  Karen C  We had a great experience! Sold our home in less than a month!  Realty One was extremely professional, friendly and great to work with. We highly recommend them!  R T M  Realty One did a fantastic job from start to finish with helping to get our house sold.  In the midst of a difficult market, they secured us an offer and sold our home within a month of listing it.  We feel like a large part of his success was the amount of websites and multimedia that they used, as well as their diligence in the details and communication between the buyer and seller. They would follow up with all of the showing agents and get feedback whenever possible. They had the research related to sales trends in our area and appropriate pricing, but didn't pressure us regarding sale price and worked with our budget.  They also continued to assist us with our next home purchase 16 hours away that had no relation to their commission.  Choosing a good Realtor is extremely important, and we were blessed to have found Realty One. Michael and Tiffany G  Realty One is an amazing Real Estate company.  They did an awesome job showing us our dream house and ensuring everything was taken care of when we went to closing.  I would highly recommend them to any of my family or friends.  Ronnie S  Realty One sold our home within six months of signing the listing agreement.  They walked us through the entire process and everything was handled without a flaw.  Pam H  Realty One has been exceptional in handling all the details for us. In my opinion, that is really the most important part of selling a home- the details.  We've been very pleased with their professionalism and work ethic! We would absolutely recommend them and will!  Bethany B  Realty One is dedicated to walking the client through each step of the process.  They are diligent and works to cover every intricate detail of the process. I would highly recommend them for any real estate need.  Matthew Y  Realty One was our agent when we sold our house in Winston-Salem. Realty One is an ideal representative.  They were professional, reliable, responsive, kind, and the list goes on.  They always did what they said they were going to do and when they said they would do it. We would definitely use Realty One again and will recommend them to others.  Jenny E  Realty One was committed to ensuring my house sold, and they are great to work with. I feel they marketed my house in a variety of ways to appeal  to prospective buyers. The virtual tour, online, contained lots of great pictures to help market the property.  They were willing to meet with me when I needed to and was readily accessible.  They were determined to sell my house while making sure I received a fair and reasonable offer in this buyers' market.  Jason K  Realty One is wonderful! They were very helpful and very knowledgeable about the current market.  Our house was listed for 18 months+ with a different broker, with little interest.  We contacted them, and they quickly provided us with a clear evaluation of our home based on local sales data.  They were able to put our house information in places not utilized by our previous broker, and the interest in our house SKY-ROCKETED.  Without Realty One our house would STILL be for sale. List with Realty One, you won’t be sorry.  Cori C  My experience working with Realty One was pleasant and rewarding.  They were able to sell my house in a short period of time when another Realtor could not sell it for over a year.  Even with the economy as bad as it has been, they were able to sell it near my asking price. I would recommend Realty One without hesitation. David K</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/realty-one-triad/realty-one-was-extremely-helpful-and-responsive-they-provid/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3a83ccf2-4606-4261-9f8b-007150b17e11</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 17:26:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/123635e7-ab02-48a4-aa02-8b50e24a9b17.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/realty-one-triad/95903bdf-0273-4ba3-a679-5d9714b049c0/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">95903bdf-0273-4ba3-a679-5d9714b049c0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 17:26:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>